Jo Smith

54 Long Street, Anytown, XP9 8JQ

jpsmith99@gmail.com

07777888999

I am a final-year maths undergraduate with customer service and sales experience in the energy industry. As a tutor and maths club coordinator I can explain maths concepts to all ages and abilities. I am keen to use my maths and commercial skills to train as an energy industry analyst.

Education

University of Birmingham (2020-2023)

BSc (Hons) Mathematics. Predicted 2:1.

Modules included mathematical modelling, mathematics in industry, real and complex analysis and mathematical finance.

Any Town High School (2013-2020)

A-levels: maths, physics, chemistry. AS-level geography.

9 GCSEs including English language and English literature.

**Employment** 

Inbound customer service adviser, Energex UK call centre (2020-2022)

Helping customers assess energy costs and tariffs

Ensuring quality and compliance standards during the switching process

Meeting and exceeding sales targets consistently

Maths tutoring for 11+ (2019-2020)

Assessing pupils level of maths and confidence in their abilities

Preparing and delivering individual lessons

100% pass rate of students

Volunteering

Coordinated Year 7 and 8 lunchtime maths club (2018-2020)

I started Maths Buzz so younger pupils could enjoy and succeed at maths. I had to publicise the group and recruit members. I also had to devise a programme of weekly activities. We had a waiting list at the end of the first term and teachers reported that pupils were achieving more in class as a result of the club.

Activities and achievements

Anytown High School Heads' Award for School Service for creating and running Maths Buzz

Duke of Edinburgh Bronze and Silver Awards.

Sports

Member of Birmingham University Cricket 2nd XI

Captain of Anytown School Cricket 1st XI

Member of Anytown Rugby Club Under 18's XV